What I really worry about sometimes is
the complexity and the jargon that we at
Cisco use.
It doesn't make any sense to me because
we come up with these runtime acronyms
which actually exclude people from the
conversation because they don't know what
you're talking about.
Because if you think about it, we have 85,
000 people.
Let's say you have a 10% turnover on the
people.
That's 8500 people a year.
In three years, that's 25,
000 people that actually are new to the
system that don't understand all the
history of Cisco.
But we have actually started talking in
this really cryptic way that then doesn't
allow them to know what's going on.
But worse yet is then we start talking
that way to customers and customers like
we're not.
When someone gives me a jargon I don't
understand,
I'm comfortable enough with my skin to
ask them, hey, what does that mean?
But a customer,
it's not that they're not comfortable,
they're not going to care to ask.
And so now what's going to happen is that
the customer doesn't understand what
we're talking about.
They'll just walk away and move on to
something else.
So the amount of damage that gets done by
us speaking in jargon and speaking in
cryptic terms is massively consequential.
And the ripple effect is pretty huge.
So my ask for everyone is speak in simple
English.
The goal is not to make sure that we
sound smart when we're talking.
The goal is to make sure that the other
person gets smart when we're talking.
And,
and that's one thing that I have a pet
peeve of.
I have, by the way,
I have masterfully failed at Cisco in my
four years here trying to change this
culture of not speaking in jargon and
acronyms.
But I am not going to give up.
I'm hoping that we can continue to kind
of keep shedding those acronyms and
actually it's OK to have acronyms that
are industry standard.
What I don't like is when we start
building acronyms internally that don't
mean anything,
just take a couple more seconds and type
the thing out.
Like whenever someone says I'm from SPG,
I'm like, I don't know what SPG is,
why can't you just type out security
Business Group?
I'm from CN,
why don't you just type out Cisco
networking?
Because what it does is it creates an
overhead that's not needed.
So that's my one area that I have a lot
of passion on because I feel like
inclusivity happens when you speak in
plain English that people can understand.